[{"answer": "Hi, Piers.", "docId": "120319pmt", "aSentId": 46, "question": "Mrs. Santorum, how are you?", "qSentId": 45}, {"answer": "That's good.", "docId": "120319pmt", "aSentId": 62, "question": "But the fact that they all prayed for you, did you feel now you've been strengthened by the power of prayer from that audience before you confront me?", "qSentId": 61}, {"answer": "Piers, Rick is amazing.", "docId": "120319pmt", "aSentId": 69, "question": "How do you think he's fairing?", "qSentId": 68}, {"answer": "I'm working on it, Piers.", "docId": "120319pmt", "aSentId": 99, "question": "You know, there's a bit of work to be done here, isn't there, Karen?", "qSentId": 98}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "120319pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "What did you think of that?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "Not at all.", "docId": "120319pmt", "aSentId": 139, "question": "Is he anti-us having contraception?", "qSentId": 138}, {"answer": "Not at all.", "docId": "120319pmt", "aSentId": 141, "question": "Well, what is his view?", "qSentId": 140}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120319pmt", "aSentId": 156, "question": "When you say he'll do nothing on the contraception issue, do you mean that if he was to become president that he would basically respect a woman's right to have contraception if that's what she chose to do?", "qSentId": 155}, {"answer": "Well, we talk a lot throughout the day, Piers.", "docId": "120319pmt", "aSentId": 177, "question": "How often do you pick that phone up and say, Rick, you shouldn't have said that?", "qSentId": 176}, {"answer": "Well, because he's a man who cares deeply about the heart and soul of America.", "docId": "120319pmt", "aSentId": 225, "question": "If he does, why should American women also love your husband?", "qSentId": 224}, {"answer": "I'm going to have to ask her.", "docId": "120319pmt", "aSentId": 324, "question": "What the hell that does that mean?", "qSentId": 323}, {"answer": "Well, I think when you're dealing in snippets with little sound bites you really don't get the full picture of -- who somebody is.", "docId": "120319pmt", "aSentId": 329, "question": "What do you think -- what do you think she meant?", "qSentId": 328}, {"answer": "I said, oh, my gosh.", "docId": "120319pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "When she was on bended knee proposing, what were you thinking?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, I believe there are good people on both sides of almost every issue in that regard.", "docId": "120319pmt", "aSentId": 397, "question": "It's getting completely out of hand and actually becoming destructive to the party?", "qSentId": 396}, {"answer": "ROWN: Well, you'd have to certainly speak to Mitt and his team.", "docId": "120319pmt", "aSentId": 445, "question": "What's the problem?", "qSentId": 444}, {"answer": "Well, I know that when it comes to dealing with the economic issues, there's no one I would trust more than Governor Romney.", "docId": "120319pmt", "aSentId": 458, "question": "Is it an issue, do you think, his friends slightly -- it frustrates you that he can't get that side over?", "qSentId": 457}, {"answer": "No phones, no iPad.", "docId": "120319pmt", "aSentId": 499, "question": "What it Gene Simmons singing through the screen?", "qSentId": 498}, {"answer": "Actually, I went to a Kiss concert.", "docId": "120319pmt", "aSentId": 502, "question": "What is it with you and Gene Simmons?", "qSentId": 501}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120319pmt", "aSentId": 602, "question": "You actually want me to comment on that?", "qSentId": 601}, {"answer": "Well, it's settled law in Massachusetts.", "docId": "120319pmt", "aSentId": 624, "question": "How do you personally feel about that?", "qSentId": 623}, {"answer": "You need to -- we need your debt and deficit under control.", "docId": "120319pmt", "aSentId": 664, "question": "How do you keep America great?", "qSentId": 663}, {"answer": "No, that's the key.", "docId": "120319pmt", "aSentId": 666, "question": "Other than that?", "qSentId": 665}, {"answer": "You need to create jobs.", "docId": "120319pmt", "aSentId": 668, "question": "Assuming you do that, what else do you do to -- to maintain America's greatness in the world?", "qSentId": 667}, {"answer": "Have the president from Apple on.", "docId": "120319pmt", "aSentId": 680, "question": "What is wrong with that?", "qSentId": 679}, {"answer": "I think that you need to make America competitive again.", "docId": "120319pmt", "aSentId": 682, "question": "What do you think of that argument?", "qSentId": 681}, {"answer": "That's it.", "docId": "120319pmt", "aSentId": 712, "question": "That's it?", "qSentId": 711}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "120319pmt", "aSentId": 716, "question": "You have so much more to say, right?", "qSentId": 715}, {"answer": "I'm good.", "docId": "120319pmt", "aSentId": 729, "question": "Frank, how are you?", "qSentId": 728}, {"answer": "You've been out there in the Green Room listening to all this, Karen Santorum and then Scott Brown.", "docId": "120319pmt", "aSentId": 731, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 730}, {"answer": "To a large extent, yes, it's been embedded in the dynamics of the Republican primary.", "docId": "120319pmt", "aSentId": 736, "question": "Is it their fault that we've been debating little else but abortion and contraception and other social issues like that?", "qSentId": 735}, {"answer": "It was interesting the way she said it.", "docId": "120319pmt", "aSentId": 752, "question": "Were you surprised to hear her say that?", "qSentId": 751}, {"answer": "Not --", "docId": "120319pmt", "aSentId": 782, "question": "Who would have a better chance of beating Barack Obama, very quickly?", "qSentId": 781}, {"answer": "Romney, Romney.", "docId": "120319pmt", "aSentId": 784, "question": "Santorum or Romney, we'll offer two?", "qSentId": 783}, {"answer": "It depends on what happens between now and then.", "docId": "120319pmt", "aSentId": 789, "question": "-- who's president?", "qSentId": 788}, {"answer": "Not doing that.", "docId": "120319pmt", "aSentId": 791, "question": "Once answer?", "qSentId": 790}]